Guide to the Jonsson Library of Government Documents Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Jonsson Library of Government Documents records
circa 1983-1993
SC1122
Jonsson Library of Government Documents
1.5 Linear feet (1 boxes)
Surveys, policies, reports, and other departmental records from the Jonsson Library of Government Documents.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, July 2012.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use.
Biographical/Historical note
The Jonsson Library of Government Documents is a part of Stanford University Libraries and Academic Information Resources. Stanford University Library was first designated a federal depository library in 1895, and a depository for California state publications in 1983. The first dedicated Documents Librarian was appointed in 1919. In 1983, what had been known as the Government Documents Department was named the Jonsson Library of Government Documents in honor of Margaret and Erik Jonsson.
The Jonsson Library collects and provides access to documents produced by U.S. federal, U.S. state and local, foreign national and local, and international governmental agencies.
Scope and Content
Surveys, policies, reports, and other departmental records from the Jonsson Library of Government Documents.
Arrangement note
Records are arranged as received from department of origin.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Libraries.; Depository libraries--California
Collection Contents
- User surveys, 1989 Dec (Box 1, Folder 1)
- User surveys, 1989 Sep (Box 1, Folder 2)
- User surveys, 1989 Jul (Box 1, Folder 3)
- User surveys, 1989 Jul (Box 1, Folder 4)
- User surveys, 1989 Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
- User surveys, 1989 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
- User surveys, 1989 Apr (Box 1, Folder 7)
- User surveys, 1989 Mar (Box 1, Folder 8)
- User surveys, 1989 Feb (Box 1, Folder 9)
- User surveys, 1989 Jan (Box 1, Folder 10)
- User surveys, 1988 Dec (Box 1, Folder 11)
- User surveys, 1988 Nov (Box 1, Folder 12)
- User surveys, 1988 Oct (Box 1, Folder 13)
- User surveys, 1988 Sep (Box 1, Folder 14)
- User surveys, 1988 Jul (Box 1, Folder 15)
- User surveys, 1988 Jun (Box 1, Folder 16)
- User surveys, 1988 May (Box 1, Folder 17)
- User surveys, 1988 Apr (Box 1, Folder 18)
- User surveys, 1988 Feb (Box 1, Folder 19)
- User surveys, 1988 Jan (Box 1, Folder 20)
- User surveys, 1987 Dec (Box 1, Folder 21)
- User surveys, 1987 Nov (Box 1, Folder 22)
- User surveys, 1987 Oct (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
- User surveys, 1987 Sep (Box 1, Folder 25)
- User surveys, 1987 Aug (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
- User surveys, 1987 May (Box 1, Folder 28)
- User surveys, 1987 Apr (Box 1, Folder 29)
- User surveys, 1987 Mar (Box 1, Folder 30)
- User surveys, 1987 Feb (Box 1, Folder 31)
- User surveys, 1987 Jan (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Collection development report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Organization charts (Box 1, Folder 34-35)
- Staff/other people (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Tech processing, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Admin policies (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Government documents: definition (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Government documents: definition task force (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Goals and objectives, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Imprint article, other descriptions (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Microforms policy (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Meetings -- staff librarians (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Librarians meetings (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Department goals (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Reorganization, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- User survey: reference/circulation, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Move, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Move, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Move (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Move, and planning for return, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- General (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Programmatic Assessment of Breaking Up the Jonsson Library, 1990 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Maps (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Conservation of government documents (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Conservation: Meyer basement flood (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Annual reports -- shelf count (Box 1, Folder 58)